If you thought Miami was rough, you haven't worked the streets of L.A.
L.A. Takedown is a crime, thriller, tv movie film directed by Michael Mann.
The tale of two skilled professionals--one a cop, the other a
criminal--who aren't as different as they think.
Vincent Hanna is an intense cop on the trail of
ruthless armed robber Patrick McLaren.
After a botched heist, the two men confront each via a full
scale battle on the seedy streets of Los Angeles.
Vincent Hanna, played by Scott Plank.
Patrick McLaren, played by Alex McArthur.
Bosko, played by Michael Rooker.
Lillian Hanna, played by Ely Pouget.
Michael Cerrito, played by Vincent Guastaferro.
Lou Casals, played by Richard Chaves.
Takedown, also called L.A.
Crimewave and Made in L.A., is a 1989 American crime action
film written and directed by Michael Mann.
Originally filmed as a pilot for an NBC television series, the project was reworked
and aired as a stand-alone TV film after the series was not picked up.
The film was later released on VHS and, in Region 2, on DVD.
The ensemble cast includes Scott Plank, Alex McArthur, Michael
Rooker, Daniel Baldwin, and Xander Berkeley.
Plank starred as Vincent Hanna, a detective on the hunt for professional criminal Patrick McLaren, played by
McArthur; the story was based on the real-life investigation of Chicago criminal Neil McCauley.
Best known as the basis for Mann's 1995 film Heat, the film has since drawn
respectable retrospective reviews, but remains overshadowed by its remake.
The tone is intense.